<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Varsha</title>
    <link>https://varsham.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Varsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 - Varsha</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:53:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://varsham.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Interviewer: Short Story #1</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p11864/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p11864/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1 - SOPHIE
The interviewees, Sophie, Theresa, Roy, and Kathryn, sat nervously at the wooden table, their trembling hands laced tightly together. Sophie was tapping her foot twice as fast as the seconds on the clock on the wall across from her, and the others watched her in silence. Suddenly, a man appeared out of the glass doorway across from them.
All four of them sat in the same room, the room with one glass window that was too tall to see from, and reflected all the light in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was the Transatlantic Slave Trade?</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p11564/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 17:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p11564/</guid>
      <description>Well, what is it? The Transatlantic slave trade occurred during the 15th century, around 1650. What do you think when you hear the word &amp;ldquo;slave &amp;ldquo;?
You might be thinking of deadly diseases, forced labor, and just brutal conditions in general. This was all true for the slaves who were forced to work during the Transatlantic slave trade, but the Africans, the people who actually started the trade, did not mean for it to turn out that way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book #1: Battle</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p11244/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 20:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p11244/</guid>
      <description>**CHAPTER 1: **
Kai grabbed a string of water from her desk and hung it up in her room. Her wings ruffled her chair, and strands of water fell off of it, turning to puddles on the floor.
&amp;ldquo;No! &amp;rdquo; cried Kai, as she gathered up the strands, quickly turning them into ropes of water again with a flick of her wrist. Her curtains, made of water, flickered, almost falling and suffering the same fate as the water ropes, but Kai dropped the strands and fixes them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandfather</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10955/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10955/</guid>
      <description>My grandfather had cancer, and he was at the last stage of it. The doctors could do nothing for him now. On the way to the hospital, to have one last time to see him, in my hand were several photographs, of an iris flower, one of his favorites, and his favorite bird - the Chestnut-sided Warbler. He told me that he had only seen it once, and that day had been the greatest day of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culprit</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10784/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 01:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10784/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Back then, 50 years ago, people used things called &amp;#8216;computers&amp;rsquo; to search things up..blah, blah, blah &amp;hellip;Scarlett! &amp;ldquo;
I look up at my red-faced teacher, suddenly awoken out of my stupor, and mutter, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Scarlett Rose. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;What did you say?! &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;I said it&amp;rsquo;s Scarlett Rose. &amp;ldquo;
My teacher finds nothing else to blame for, so, still red-faced, she goes back to her lesson. &amp;ldquo;They also used &amp;#8216;electricity&amp;rsquo; for light &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay the Price</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10684/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10684/</guid>
      <description>MERILEE MAXWELL
Prologue
I finger the child&amp;rsquo;s hair, and she looks up at me, all bundled up in those blankets her parents gave her, her eyes red with tears. They&amp;rsquo;ll be waiting for their precious Araceli, I know. They will be waiting.
I lean backward, peering out of the sterile white door, and I catch a glimpse of _them: _ Xander and Rylee. Rylee&amp;rsquo;s hair is a mess of wispy brown flyaway, and she is clutching Xander&amp;rsquo;s hand, and grinning like an idiot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YAC STRY 6th Grade</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10544/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10544/</guid>
      <description>Crack! I hear the crack of the whip from outside, and my mother storms in, her face as red as the bricks on our fireplace. I know to avoid her at times like this, and I dodge the storming feet and the flailing hands, and especially, the whip. I run outside to our beautiful mansion, with a temptation to stop by the endearing little pond next to the mansion, but I resist it with a little regret, because I had many chores to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am a Creative and Music-Loving Girl</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10364/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10364/</guid>
      <description>I am a creative and music-loving girl
I feel excited about possibilities everywhere.
I dream that I&amp;rsquo;ve built a solution to a persistent problem,
and I pretend that these imagined creations could materialize before me,
and I hope that I can make a good impact on the world.
I am a creative and music-loving girl.
When I go outside, I see the families of birds twittering excitedly in their nests,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterpiece</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p10274/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p10274/</guid>
      <description>The rich deep blue
is a masterpiece.
As if an artist is weaving a large brush over his endless canvas.
Or the sunset yellows, or bright orange,
whichever the artist chooses
is shown to all of Earth at different times.
The darker night
dotting the bluish-black sky
with the delicacy of stars
lighting up the night.
Whichever the artist chooses,
it is a masterpiece.
Whether it is the rising sun penetrating the once dark blue</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flutist</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9831/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 23:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9831/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loved Robert, who could play the flute so beautifully and make his fingers fly and his legs dance, and Robert’s twin sister Darlene always welcomed the children that would drift towards his house to hear him play. He was the brightest silver lining our town ever had.
Robert was a friend of my mother, ever since we had moved here. He had cheered me up with his songs when I was sad, and he made Katie’s and my life as sweet as chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick write</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9551/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 21:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9551/</guid>
      <description>Rough Draft – “Clinton and Trump”
My question about this article is about the subtitle “Trump Wants Stricter Rules”. My confusion about these paragraphs is about the temporary ban of Muslims entering the United States. How will temporarily banning Muslims from entering the country help with solving the problem? I say this because members of a violent Islamic group could already be in the United States, disguised. Another reason is that the article says two things about Muslims fleeing from this Islamic group that prove my point: “Many Muslims are trying to escape the violent group, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures of Edward Tulane</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9431/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9431/</guid>
      <description>The Adventures of Edward Tulane is an awesome book. I think this because of the author&amp;rsquo;s way of moving through the plot- not too fast and not too slow. I also loved the feelings the author put between the lines.
Summary: Edward Tulane was a china rabbit that was owned by a ten year old girl named Abilene. She loved him very much, but the rabbit didn&amp;rsquo;t love her as much as she did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick write(4th Grade)</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9391/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 21:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9391/</guid>
      <description>5-25-16
Dear Little Brother/Sister, (Note: I don’t have a little brother or sister)
You’ve asked me over and over again what a budget is. Well, now I’m here to tell you. First of all, what is a budget? A budget is something that you create that you can use to plan out how you will spend your money. For example, consider that puzzle you’ve always wanted. But you have to consider that you need to get a certain reading book for school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Frog</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9161/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 22:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9161/</guid>
      <description>I have a pet frog that has amazing acuity. The frog zeroes in on one of its &amp;ldquo;prey &amp;ldquo;(frog food) and waits until it thinks that the food won&amp;rsquo;t be alert when it catches it. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where my little frog came from, but I like to imagine that during the &amp;ldquo;Age of Immigration &amp;rdquo; a group of immigrants came and had the frog with them. The frog had escaped to the pet shop, and here I am, watching my frog&amp;rsquo;s acuity catch prey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Tragic Disasters</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 23:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9121/</guid>
      <description>Two notorious wildfires had raged through the USA. The earliest of these wildfires occurred in June, 1988. That fateful proved to be a very terrible day for everyone at that time. Three years later, in October, 1991, another wildfire erupted in Oakland, California. This day also proved to be terrible.
In Wyoming, Yellowstone park officials were suffering many firs. But none of the fires were major. Even so, firefighters were sent out to battle every blaze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perilous Journey of Sediment</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 00:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9011/</guid>
      <description>Hi. I’m Sediment. I used to sit for a long time on this big tall pointy thing. My brothers and sisters have been cruelly taken by…Wind! I’ve been tossed around a lot by him, and believe me, you would NOT like it. It’s like being in those flying things that go around in the air all the time, except you are being roughhoused. Right now I am relaxing on a bunch of other sediment people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8981/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8981/</guid>
      <description>Snow falls
Like angels from the sky
Drifting softly down
Onto the snow-strewn ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature’s Cycle</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8931/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8931/</guid>
      <description>The seed grows,
The green sprouts emerge from the earth
Like reluctant school children
On a first day of school
But when the thunder strikes
The lightning illuminates the silent night
Terrible rains pour down
Like children swarming out at their recess time
But the sprouts stay
Leaves slowly grow
Their color bright green
With the radiance of a freshly painted piece of art.
The sprouts grow
into a small tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Kid</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8721/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8721/</guid>
      <description>Hello.
My name is Mary Fieldson.
I’m 9, and I’m in 4th grade.
I have 3 brothers. Their names are: Daniel, Tyler, and Jacob. My dad used to work from some really early time to some really late time, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t really see him often. My mother was the one who convinced my dad to take a new job and move to Florida. She grew up in Florida. She really enjoys the warm weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unhealthy School Lunches: What do you think?</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8691/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 15:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8691/</guid>
      <description>I think that unhealthy school lunches should not be allowed because they can cause diabetes. This disease does not have cure and it is developed by obesity. Obesity is developed from the eating of fried or oily foods, such as the foods in Haley&amp;rsquo;s cafeteria. Haley is a person who has a cafeteria that serves unhealthy lunches. According to the article I read, Haley&amp;rsquo;s lunch menu for that day was french fries, hot dogs, and pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer of the Swans: By Betsy Byars</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 00:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8621/</guid>
      <description>Summer of the Swans is a book with very happy ending. I loved this book because when the second-most main character got lost in the woods, the tension of panic rose.
Summary:After Sara had taken Charlie, her mentally handicapped brother, to see the swans nearby, he fell in love with them. During the night, he was itching to go to the swans but he did not know the way, so he got lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8571/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8571/</guid>
      <description>Annelise was an orphan. She was kind and loved animals. Her mother, who had died a long time ago from a sickness, was so kind, too. Everyone mourned at her death.
Her father had built her the house she lived in currently before he collapsed on his deathbed and died. Weeks after the house was built, people looking for places to build their houses got attracted to the little house and built their houses right there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Meteor Showers Fall</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8541/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8541/</guid>
      <description>The demons wanted to make possible an evil plan to cause destruction to the mortals, for they wanted Vishnu, the protector of the universe, to beg for pity. They wanted to show that they were stronger. They were so tired of losing against Vishnu. For the first time they wanted to win, because Vishnu was their archenemy. During the debate of what they should do, one demon suggested putting a layer of rocks on all of the skies of Earth so that living things down on Earth could not breathe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Body Defenses: Just the Basic Facts</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8521/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 01:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8521/</guid>
      <description>First, one defense is the skin. It keeps the germs from attacking the body organs. There is one way that germs can pass through the skin: If there is an open cut in the skin, the germs have a way to the body and making you sick.
Earwax is the 2nd body defense. It is in everyone&amp;rsquo;s ears to trap the germs who try to get the ear, trying to damage the delicate organs in the ear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Columbian Exchange: Opinion Writing</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8491/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 15:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8491/</guid>
      <description>The Columbian Exchange occurred hundreds of years ago. There were two worlds at that time: The Old World and The New World. The Old World consisted of 3 continents: Europe, Africa, and Asia. The New World consists of 2 continents: North America and South America. These two continents were called the Americas.. When Columbus and future explorers traded items with the Americas that lived in the Americas, this was called the Columbian Exchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Basic Facts#3</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 17:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8101/</guid>
      <description>I will be introducing you to the topic: eyelashes!!! Focus Question: What is the whole purpose of eyelashes? Answer: Eyelashes direct the flow of air out of your eyes. To clarify what I mean by that, eyelashes help keep your eyes moist, or slightly damp. Did you know that 22 species of animals rely on their eyelashes for the same reason? Bet you didn&amp;rsquo;t! From humans to horses to elephants, they all have the same reason the rely on their eyelashes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Basic Facts#2</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8081/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8081/</guid>
      <description>Like art? Well, then this is the article for you! By the way, Just the Basic Facts is a series of informational articles. Come on my website to see a new, equally exciting, article!
The star of this article is: Marta Alonso Yebra!
Marta was an art student. She grew up into a Spanish architect who had very interesting ideas! No wonder! The spark started at Marta&amp;rsquo;s childhood, when she was an art student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just the Basic Facts#1</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8051/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 23:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8051/</guid>
      <description>Hello, ladies and gentlemen! I am very happy to share an article that I am proudly presenting before you:
How Hurricanes Are Named
Hurricanes come to us in various different ways. Because of these changes, they get different names. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me how meteorologists detect the similarity, but they do! First, when a hurricane comes in, they name the hurricane. Boy names and girl names alternate, going back and forth into a pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Home by Joan Bauer</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p8001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 16:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p8001/</guid>
      <description>Almost Home makes me feel as if I had just eaten a warm chocolate. Joan Bauer wrote in a colloquial style, with added a beautiful effect. Written by Joan Bauer, this story touched my heart.
Sugar Mae Cole had a father that she didn&amp;rsquo;t trust. He owed many people, including her grandfather, King Cole. But trouble flares after his death. 12-year-old Sugar Cole loses her home, and her mother shuts down, and Sugar&amp;rsquo;s dreary result was that she was left alone, and she had much to experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7871/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 20:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7871/</guid>
      <description>When I hold my oboe
I feel a ripple of satisfaction
Slowly creeping its way up
When I purse my lips
I blow hopefully
And a cool, clear sound blasts out
creating a second ripple of satisfaction
I struggle
But that is key to satisfaction
That is how one learns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing the Line</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7811/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 20:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7811/</guid>
      <description>There are many
who cross the line
and once they do
they never come back
Tis&amp;rsquo; the line of good and bad
When one becomes bad
They never become good
When you cross that line
that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist
You have no meaning
Your heart becomes rocky
Never feeling any touch of love
Unless you change
Until your soul forgives you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cycle of Nature</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7791/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 13:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7791/</guid>
      <description>The snow falls
like angels from heaven
Soft and dainty
Falling on the grass
Which was once green
Until spring comes
The snow melts away
showing the grass once again
With that full green color
Finally it&amp;rsquo;s summer
The vapor greets us
Beads of sweat drip down our backs
Slapping away mosquitos
In summer, the stores with the repellent
Are in low supply
School&amp;rsquo;s out
Finally it&amp;rsquo;s fall
School starts again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic on the Stage</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7741/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 20:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7741/</guid>
      <description>I jumped for joy when I heard that I would be seeing the middle school play. My sister was not as excited as me, nor my mother. We would be seeing Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, a story which I have read for hours for my passion for it was strong. I used to read it so many times, although it was quite a large book.
Finally, I steeped out of the car, releived for the ride seemed to take long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opinions About Amelia Earhart</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7651/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 15:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7651/</guid>
      <description>Amelia Earhart, a rising female flier, is taking lessons from Neta Snook, a renowned flier. When Neta Snook first laid her eyes on the white-gloved lady, she thought, “More silly people with silly questions.” However, she soon realized that Amelia only wanted Neta to instruct her in the field of flying. Amelia started taking lessons with Neta beginning on the third of January, 1921.
On the first lesson, Amelia arrives wearing khaki pants, boots, a colorful scarf, and a knee length jacket which she has slept in for several nights to give it a used look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Tree in London</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 23:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7611/</guid>
      <description>The dot grows
The green sprouts emerge from the earth
like reluctant school children
But when the thunder strikes
The lightening lights up the stilled night
Rains pour down
Like constant floods
But the sprouts stay
The sprouts grow
into a small tree
like the broccoli that we eat
But then the large winds blow
The tree falters
But it still stands strong
The roots grow
expanding wider
each week</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Time Has Come</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7561/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 23:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7561/</guid>
      <description>GRANDPA
A worry line
creased Grandpa&amp;rsquo;s weary face
when he left Alexis to her fate
The one who stayed by his side
For all the years to come,
he hoped that she would face it
ALEXIS
I hope
Grandpa&amp;rsquo;ll be all right
Since Denise died
I could not face it
Why me?
Denise
She was so kind
She suffered my pain with me
Until her end
GRANDPA
Grandpa was down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Amazing Land (ooh!) of Rain Forests (ahhh!)</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7481/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 19:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7481/</guid>
      <description>Rain Forests: An Introduction
You are in the rainforest. The beautiful green trees tower above you. Beads of sweat form on your face and neck. Your arms are sticky from the large amount of humidity. You are in a rain forest.
Each day is predictable. The rain falls for about 4 inches each day.
People
Rain forest people thrive in the rain forests. They feed on plants from the rain forests, such as berries, plantains, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annelise&#39;s Story</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7431/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 21:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7431/</guid>
      <description>Annelise lived in a lovely seaside town in Ocean City. Her mother had died a long time ago from a sickness, so Annelise had to stay in this house. She had moved here when she finished her schooling. But she had an ambition: writing.
Her father had built the little house she lived in, and this drew attention to the ones living in the hotels to live in houses of your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Someday ...</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7391/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7391/</guid>
      <description>My home. Denmark. A village of beauty. The sky always had that forget-me-not blue in the mornings. The sun glowed bright yellow. In the night-times, there was a beautiful blackish bluish color in the dark sky. The stars twinkled like far away lanterns, and the moon glowed a gray color, filled with sweetness of no other kind. In the mornings, the morning dew sparkled on the bright green grass. A young tree in front our house had birds chirping all over it in their nests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helena (Book #1)</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7321/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7321/</guid>
      <description>The little girl was a baby when they left. Her parents had been on a trip. They never came back, even when seven years passed. Every year, Helena had asked Anna, her old housekeeper when her parents would be coming back, and Anna always answered they would always come back.
But that stopped when Anna passed away three years ago.
Since she was 7 years old, Helena was left to live with her horrid uncle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I was a Superhero!</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7281/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7281/</guid>
      <description>Quick Write 3-23-15
If I was a superhero, I would want to be able to conjure up anything that I want. I would want to have this ability because then, it would be easy for me to save many lives. Another power I would like is the ability to time travel to any place I want. I would want this power because if I time traveled back to the Revolutionary War, I could save many people from dying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dream</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7251/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 16:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7251/</guid>
      <description>She escaped from Salem
Ever since her mother was a witch to them
She never believed in them
But they did
The people of Salem
She was afraid
She was inconsolable
for she had loved her mother
more than the world itself
She was sad and alone
An orphan
She dreamt
in her lonely fort
that she could stop
the dangerous people of Salem
Starting at her youth
To stop the superstitious people</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 16:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7221/</guid>
      <description>The snow falls
It touches the ground
Like angels
being sent from god
I open my mouth
The cool snow touches my tongue
It melts away
I shiver
The snow is cold
Brrr
It&amp;rsquo;s time for me to come inside
My mother makes hot chocolate
I sip it
Warm and happyz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Revenge of Bronchus</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 14:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7141/</guid>
      <description>CLARENCE
Clarence hovered over her studies, her experiments. She was a robotics scientist.
Suddenly she had an idea.
It would be the greatest one yet.
Her project.
In a matter of minutes, Clarence had created her life long dream.
The robot moved and waved his hand. &amp;ldquo;Hi. &amp;ldquo;
BRONCHUS(BROHN-KUS) Centuries later &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.
He was a robot. He was named Bronchus.
Bronchus turned to a Canadian robot and asked him to ring the bell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Uppercase Letter Poem</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 13:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7041/</guid>
      <description>It all began with A(drum roll):_
_ A is some cool gymnastics equipment
and B you can climb on,
C turned a certain angle you can slide on,
D is a house
of all your dreams
and E and B are brothers
F always
Tries to be like E
But she is almost there
G is a gymnast
so flexible
H a comfy bed
That children go to at
bedtime,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p7021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 13:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p7021/</guid>
      <description>I live in the suburbs. Whenever I go outside, I hear the deep barking of dogs. In the evenings, it smells like after a bonfire. On my section of the street, there are the perfect hiding places, so Hide and Go Seek is a popular game in my circle of friends. There are lots of trees fit for climbing, and in one of my friend&amp;rsquo;s backyard, there were 2 swings. They took 1 of the swings down, because the trees was rotting where it hung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India: A Memory</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6991/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 13:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6991/</guid>
      <description>I remember going to India four years ago(I am nine years old). I loved that place because there were so many things to see. The bustling streets aroused my spirits, and the small shops sold awesome things cheap! Sometimes Pedama would let my sister and I buy anything we liked in those small shops.
The cars sprouted dust onto the orange-ish roads. I also always hear the cars rumbling on the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Revolutionary War</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6971/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 12:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6971/</guid>
      <description>British and America
declared war,
on 1775
one day before
April&amp;rsquo;s 20th
That&amp;rsquo;s when the guns raised
Independence
was a great struggle
when each took their side,
Soldiers were enlisted
from everyplace
Just to protect the country
All with different names
one great leader
that lead America
by the great name of George
Washington led his group
all the way in Valley Forge
The soldiers felt like wrangling
talked spiteful things behind his back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhodopus (Book #2)</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6901/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 02:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6901/</guid>
      <description>Rhodopus had went on a trip to some sort of mystic cliffs and mountains and, quite accidentally, was hanging off a very strong cliff rock. Her cold hands gripped the bumps and the holes that were formed inside the rock very long ago.
She was so frightened that she thought that she would have rather fell and died rather than keep gripping onto that rock.
Well, reader, you might be asking why she was hanging of a rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arenelle&#39;s Quest</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6791/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 15:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6791/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1-THE BEGINNING ♣ It the far away lands of Leafland, there live a little girl named Arenelle. Arenelle was a little girl by the age of 9. At night Arenelle always heard her parents talking about someone named Marielle. Arenelle never paid attention to this, but little did she know that Marielle was a lost sister of hers. Finally, when Arenelle turned 11, her parents revealed the painful secret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Where The Mountain Meets The Moon</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6701/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 17:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6701/</guid>
      <description>This story is full of hope and adventure.
I like that this is not a no-problem story. I also like that there is never an obvious solution to the problems.
Summary:
Minli&amp;rsquo;s family is poor. But when Ba tells tells the story of the Old Man Of The Moon, Minli is determined to help her family to get a fortune. So Minli sets off. During her journey,she meets a fish that can talk, a dragon that is not able to fly, and a powerful king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Thing That Satisfies Me</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6671/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 14:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6671/</guid>
      <description>Me,at school,
hungry
not for food,
but for something
that cannot be expressed
Me at lunch,
hungry
not for food
but for some people
that cannot be shared
Me at class again
hungry
not for food,
but for a feeling
that cannot be shown
Me at the next class
hungry
not for food
but for something
that cannot be replaced
Me at home
No hunger
not because of food,
but for my family,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6651/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 14:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6651/</guid>
      <description>Mother, like the beautiful purple raven in the sky
That raven is sturdy and strong, but gentle
Father, like the consistent eagle
persisting to keep flying
like the hard work you do
Sister, like the warm and welcoming wren
Cordial than any other
Me, like the slinky
unable to stop my fidgeting
Unless my family&amp;rsquo;s around</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6611/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 14:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6611/</guid>
      <description>Love
A wonderful thing indeed,
Unable to be shown
Can only be expressed
But there is a deeper meaning for love
That secret is the love between family
And the never-ending love
between the daughter and the mother in this family</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Review of The Trumpet of the Swan_ by E.B.White</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6551/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 01:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6551/</guid>
      <description>This story is very heartwarming and endearing.
Summary:
Two swans give birth to 5 cygnets, including one that has speech defect. His name is Louis.Then Louis falls in love with a beautiful swan by the name of Serena. Sadly, because of his speech defect, Serena does not pay any attention to him.
Louis learns to read and write at a certain school. Louis then tries to use his writing talent to win Serena&amp;rsquo;s love, but they find out that Serena does not know how to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight&#39;s Story BOOK 3</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 23:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6481/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am the knight. A boy knight. I have the handsome head of a war horse. I am as strong as those knights that ride on those war horses. I can withstand anyone that traverses my path. My cousin Pawna, is the youngest of all. I don&amp;rsquo;t really talk with any of her 6 siblings and their mother, and so has the others. The pawns look like their mother. Bishoppa the bishop, on the other hand, is my smart, kind, cousin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6441/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 22:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6441/</guid>
      <description>I was so small then
But I did know
Father
Just grabbing his suitcase
Out the door
To the world
Where I could never find him
I looked at Mother
A tear rolling down her cheek
I could tell
It was a tear of sadness mixed with anger
I ran upstairs
Sobs bursting out
Years passed
A ring from the doorbell
We&amp;rsquo;ve haven&amp;rsquo;t had one in ages
I opened the door</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of Poems</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6411/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6411/</guid>
      <description>Mother
Oh! Of all
The mothers,
Have you known, that you are the best?
Extrodinary mother
Running with magic like no other
Father
**A ** hard worker, in what way can I
Thank him
He works so hard
Extrodinary
Running with the magic of love
Sister
**I ** love her
She is a little sister&amp;rsquo;s best friend
Thank her, because of her
Extrodinary help
Running with magic of friendship</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6371/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 00:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6371/</guid>
      <description>WHAT IS EMPATHY?
Empathy is everything to everyone. Even the evil. Empathy is like the desired gold to humans. But not many people have empathy.
Empathy is a certain type of kindness. It is but a special type of kindness. There is also this kindness called sympathy. Being sympathetic is easier to be than empathetic. But let me explain about sympathy. Sympathy is when you are sorry for a person. Empathy is when you feel sorry for a person and you do something out of kindness for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6331/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6331/</guid>
      <description>I see it It’s uncontrollable The urge to pick it up Picturing Predicting what’s going to happen Immersed Forgetting the surroundings Those details They carry the clues on their backs Having hope Will it ever get better? Curiously waiting for the solution Questions pop up Wonder can’t wait any longer I can see the hero The villains too One against many Finally &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; A rush of happiness &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; I see a splash of colors &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Bright and cheerful &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; I relax with an amazing ending &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Finally closing the book &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p style=&amp;quot;text-align: center&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Full of satisfaction &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pawna the Pawn</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6301/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 17:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6301/</guid>
      <description>I am the pawn. A girl pawn, to be specific. My name is Pawna. We always do this thing called chess. The queen says it is a game, but I don’t think it is. I don’t like it, mainly because I and the other pawns are always in the front row! I tried talking Bishop into switching spaces with me, but he never fell for it.
“Pawna!” It’s the queen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6271/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2014 18:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6271/</guid>
      <description>Katherine couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get to witch school. There were wisps that fluttered around, and they made very good jokes. but these wisps were very wise, too. They what the correct decision was all the time. Katherine relied on themin her past years. Katherine climbed up on her broom and chanted the enchanted spell to make the broom take her o school. several minutes flew by. Katherine&amp;rsquo;s long auburn hair whipped her face i the fast movement of the wind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6211/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6211/</guid>
      <description>I was a spring girl. I control the weather in spring. Mother was the controller of fall, my father was the controller of spring and winter. That is why father was dull when he was sad, to resemble his winter powers, and he was extremely excited when he was happy, to resemble his spring powers. Mother was like any human mother, because fall is in the middle of hot and cold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6181/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 01:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6181/</guid>
      <description>There once lived 2 girls in a village. Both of them thought that no one else was their age in that dreary place. Their mothers made them wash the clothes and do other tedious things, so they never got a chance to explore anything. Elaine was one of the girls, and was finally bored of her chores. To activate her plan, she sneaked out of the washing parlor and ran off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gittilian Leisure News 1</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p6111/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 23:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p6111/</guid>
      <description>Wednsday, October 15, 2014 CLOVERLAND UNDER TOTAL DESTRUCTION
Cloverland has been air-raided by enemies. The land&amp;rsquo;s pretty features were deleted from vision. The residents are in dilemma. Queen Kate isn&amp;rsquo;t helping. Queen Athena was busy in her land, so the residents are mystified by the crude behavior of the queen. The queen was not appeared to adopt the land since Queen Athena gave her land. The residents are begging Athena for a solution, but Athena is afraid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspired</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5991/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5991/</guid>
      <description>Those letters on
that keyboard
that screen
that glows
delicate
makes my imagination
bloom
He bought those
Electronic devices
Open up
The laptop
Your mind is
full
You click
and type
Your school project
needs some
research
Your hands automatically
press the keys
He inspired me
Trying to find his way
Going to work
Coming back
He is a software engineer
rushes in
just to meet us
A smiling DADDY</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senseless Book 1 #</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5791/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 20:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5791/</guid>
      <description>The fairy flew along the bushes, giving her scratches. She was a new fairy, and the other fairies just learned her name.
&amp;ldquo;Alice! Come over here! There&amp;rsquo;s a caterpillar! &amp;ldquo;
Caterpillars were very rare. Alice was soon staring at awe at the caterpillar. The friends soon got bored and walked off. Suddenly, a black figure knocked Alice to the ground. He akwardly tangled it&#39;s legs in hers. Alice fell fast asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rickshaw Girl</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5721/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 14:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5721/</guid>
      <description>RICKSHAW GIRL
Naima realizes that her father doesn&amp;rsquo;t get much rest. She is worried that he won&amp;rsquo;t be able to drive the rickshaw anymore if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t get rest. Saleem, her friend, helps Naima pretend to be a boy with his clothes. When her father is gone, Naima tries to drive the rickshaw, but it only got scratches and dents all over it. Naima&amp;rsquo;s mother is very upset with her. But when she walks out in her boy clothes to find a job, a woman owner of a paintings place let her work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Away</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5631/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5631/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer called to her other 2 sisters. &amp;ldquo;Clara! Flora! &amp;rdquo; Jennifer could yell loud. &amp;ldquo;Ms.Kinderly invited us to her house! We know that her children are our friends! &amp;rdquo; Ms.Kinderly was the widow whose husband left her after the birth of her 2 children, Caroline, the youngest, and Ayanna, the oldest. Ms.Kinderly liked the children that often came to her house. 10 year old Jennifer caught sight of her 5 year old sister, Clara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strawberries</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5561/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5561/</guid>
      <description>Sweet
juicy
yummy
strawberries
eat them up!
More better news!
Time to go strawberry picking!
We ride on the bumpy road
Just cannot sit still
with such excitement!
Finally!
We&amp;rsquo;re there!
Plucking the strawberries,
They&amp;rsquo;re so good!
Save them for chocolate
dipping,
When we reach home
Chocolate
dipping is the
best of all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drama</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5531/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 15:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5531/</guid>
      <description>Spotlights
twisting and turning
hot stage
costumes
sweat
nervous
remember
scared
don&amp;rsquo;t forget
change
costumes
quickly
remind myself
play begins
first on stage
forgetting lines
looking at one another
standing still
calm
stay calm
Off stage
finally off stage
change quickly
on stage
all together
music
don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid
sad part
end of show
bowing low
loud clapping
call our names
characters too
each and
every
one
in the play</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keena Ford</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 23:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5471/</guid>
      <description>Keena Ford goes to second grade and wrote down the date wrong. Her teacher, Mrs.Campbell, mistakes her birthday for another date! What is Keena going to do now? Read the book to find out.
I liked this book because it was funny to read what mistakes the spunky main character did.
I did not like this book because it was to short.�  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnotizer</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5441/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 23:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5441/</guid>
      <description>My friend got
a hypnotizer
around and around it goes
Makes you &amp;hellip;nevermind &amp;hellip;..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bird</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5391/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 23:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5391/</guid>
      <description>Flying
glowing
zipping
hiding
the little bird opens it&amp;rsquo;s beak
feeding her babies
tiny and small
cute
resting in the twig nest
feeding on worms
slimy
squirmy
flashing red
a cardinal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5321/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 22:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5321/</guid>
      <description>I am an orphan. I&amp;rsquo;d rather be alone than be adopted. This is my story. For the beginning, I was adopted. I was 8 years old. I always dreamed of doing ridiculous things. I was a dreamer. Adventurous. I cried on the the first day I lived with my mother and father. I always curled up into a ball and slept in my room. When it was my 9th birthday, I got the courage to say something very sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conquering King Grandolfer</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 02:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5111/</guid>
      <description>The kind widow finally had a daughter, and Gretel was excited. Gretel was the widow, and she liked pretty things, so she named her Michelle. Evil King Grandolfer, he liked making his people&amp;rsquo;s life miserable. This evil king will come later in this story, so pay attention. Michelle grew up to love her mother, for Gretel was willing to help her. Unfortunately, Gretel got sick, and Michelle had to manage on her own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5171/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5171/</guid>
      <description>Oh! Licorice and candy canes
and Trick or Treat was a fame
It ought to be a shame
that it comes every year
there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to fear
on Old&amp;rsquo;Hallows&amp;rsquo;Eve
Ghosts, Princess&amp;rsquo;s
so many dresses
to Wear
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to glare
on Halloween
&amp;#8216;Cause you stuff your mouth with sweets
You never have to eat meats
&amp;#8216;Cause all you need
and all you feed
on are sweets!
But here the dark side comes,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disappearence</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p5031/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p5031/</guid>
      <description>The little girl ran breathlessly through the spring air, feeling fresh. Her land, Leafland, was always like that. “March, calm down!” said her father as she almost knocked him over. Her name was March, and she had a shiny white smile with her. 10 year old March collected leaves for her grandfather’s leaf necklace studio and crept up silently to his door.She then burst open with her shiny white smile. After a bit of laughter, March’s Grandfather went to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equality</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4991/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 17:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4991/</guid>
      <description>I was a knight. A training knight, to be specific. There are lots of other training knights, and GLADIATORS. Our school is called Knights And Armor.
{mar-veena-fill-eea} It is really awesome for a 17 year old like me to enjoy. There are armor rooms, sword rooms, and practice rooms. This is my 2nd year here. I started when I was 16. There are also long, twisting, hallways. &amp;ldquo;Richardson! &amp;rdquo; I quickly turned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Knights And Gladiators Come Together</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4831/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 01:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4831/</guid>
      <description>I was a knight. A training knight, to be specific.This is the Rennaissance time. All the Gladiators would pick on us. Especially Alex. I always secretly hope that we can defeat them soon. But that will never happen. I had sweat all over my face at the end of class because I was thinking so hard about this. On the way home, I accidently bumped into a gladiator. My big mistake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programs</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4811/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 16:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4811/</guid>
      <description>Makkapati Library
We will show the audience a play of the book HOW ELEPHANTS CAME. April 6th to April 14th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 5# Different Than Before</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4781/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 16:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4781/</guid>
      <description>I just could not wait to go to the wonderful adventure that was half explained to about the jewel in India. I think I am going there how it is right now. I climbed out of bed, then I picked up the dolphin, then shrunk, then climbed inside. I climbed through the hole at the bottom. That was when I realized that the crack was closed! I tried to rub around where the crack was and I pushed that part, but nothing budged!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 3# Ode to the Shee</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4681/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 20:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4681/</guid>
      <description>I called for mom. It was a school day and I had to go to Ireland. Luckily, time would not pass while I was there. I had readied up my backpack, and I asked my mom if I could go now. She said yes, so I went. I took the dolphin decoration with me. I shrunk, then climbed inside. Then I climbed out of the crack, then found Gwendolyne at the Shee Amusement Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 2# Strange Start</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4661/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 15:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4661/</guid>
      <description>I picked up the dolphin and shrunk. Then I climbed inside. I climbed through the crack I had made the day before. It was summer in Ireland, and I set off to find Gwendolyne. But something blocked me and made me tumble into the crack. Scratches came on my arms, and oh! Were they painful! I scooted to the back of the dolphin. Finally, the black thing went away from the crack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 1 #  Meeting the Shee</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4611/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 15:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4611/</guid>
      <description>I picked up my mother&amp;rsquo;s dolphin decoration. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know why it was here when it was first standing on my mom&amp;rsquo;s nightstand. It was so eerie. suddenly, the grass grew up and up until it towered over me. I slipped inside the hole at the bottom of the dolphin. I was almost fully inside until my mom picked it up. I grew frantic. I did not get enough time! I clung desperately to the edge of the hole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Was Inspired</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4581/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 00:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4581/</guid>
      <description>I went to the woods and climbed a tree. I fell down and felt a branch on the bottom of my thigh. Then I fell to solid ground. My sister started gasping while I was moaning. She got mom. My mom took me to the hospital. During all that time, I had my eyes closed. My mother was frantic. After all the healing, I ended up with an artificial leg. I tried walking, but I fell down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Wait!!!</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4531/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 00:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4531/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t wait. I just can&amp;rsquo;t wait!!
I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for spring, which has the beautiful blossoms and the green grass, oh, the green grass!
It is as fresh as it can be! The trees have beautiful green leaves! I of course can&amp;rsquo;t wait for those!
The happy children run in the open space and cry for outdoor playing at home!
Oh, just how can I wait for these wonderful things!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life&#39;s Magical Way</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p4111/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 16:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p4111/</guid>
      <description>Alice turned around and was startled to see her mother right there. She showed an impish smile. &amp;ldquo;Alice, how many times have I told you to not reveal that impish grin? Those manners are not perfect for a queen&amp;rsquo;s daughter. &amp;rdquo; Queen Cheryl and King Dexter were rulers of Nappinville. Their daughter, Alice, [Princess Alice] was very impish since she was 3. Alice was 19 years old. &amp;ldquo;Today is my birthday, so I am 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Ice Fairy Book # 8</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3801/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 17:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3801/</guid>
      <description>Anna went outside and climbed the tree. She did not see Caroline. Anna looked around for her. She was worried that Caroline might be trapped with the aliens again. Suddenly, Caroline tumbled down from the tree. Anna was frightened from the fall of her friend, even though she had a cushion under her wings. But Caroline was giggling madly as she stood up on her feet. Anna couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop giggling too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gittolians characters Purple Faced Thrasher</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3731/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 22:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3731/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surprise  book # 7</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3681/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3681/</guid>
      <description>Anna was in fairyland and she saw a sign that said spin around 3 times. Anna spun then she saw Egropestel&amp;rsquo;s aliens. Anna threw ice flowers at the aliens. One of the aliens died. An alien said. &amp;ldquo;We will get your friend Caroline and you will never see her! &amp;rdquo; Anna was led to a room where Caroline was strung with heavy twine. The ropes were suffocating her. Also, Anna realized the room (which was all made of heat) had ice tracks from her feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Adventurer Book#6</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3631/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 16:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3631/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anna was up the tree, she heard Caroline saying, &amp;ldquo;Spin three times to go to your adventure. &amp;rdquo; Anna spun three times and in a long time (She is in a whirlwind and it takes long time). Anna read the sign, SNOW-ATOM ADVENTURE FOR ICE! . Anna ran along and saw some Ice Controls. She made a mountain which broke them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She then came across a monster. It said, &amp;ldquo;I am Marmalade! I love ice fairies! &amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You are Heat? &amp;rdquo; asked Anna.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, &amp;rdquo; answered Marmalade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna made an ice sheet and shot it to Marmalade. When the ice quickly melted, Marmalade died.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna was surprised to see some more Ice Controls. Again, she made a mountain to destroy them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, she cried,  &amp;ldquo;I want to go back to Fairyland! I wish I could! &amp;rdquo; In a whirl wind, Anna was laying on a bed of leaves. She woke up to find her friend Caroline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You are safe from your adventure. Always remember your adventures with Marmalade. You are so brave! I am proud of you! &amp;rdquo; said Caroline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://varsham.azurewebsites.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/photo.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;size-medium wp-image-3641 alignleft&#34; alt=&#34;photo&#34; src=&#34;http://varsham.azurewebsites.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/photo-300x224.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;224&#34; srcset=&#34;http://varsham.azurewebsites.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/photo-300x224.jpg 300w, http://varsham.azurewebsites.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/photo.jpg 320w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo Club</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3291/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3291/</guid>
      <description>Oh the Kangaroo Club!
The jump roping Club,
I jumped as long as a 4th grader,
That is just the small facts so let me tell you a story.
I did not think I COULD do it,
But as my heart pounded and thudded and worked,
I just started to take it easy.
One stopped at the 2nd grade point,
While I JUMPED AND JUMPED so long that my chest started arguing with me,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great sister</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3231/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 02:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3231/</guid>
      <description>My sister jumps up,
Her jovial face lightens up,
I laugh in too,
Both entering our mischievous ways,
Sister, I love you so,
As I play with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairy School for Anna</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2881/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2881/</guid>
      <description>Anna climbed up the trees she had met last time. It was the sessions of Fairy School. When Anna climbed up, she saw that she was shrinking! When she was her tiny size, she had wings and a wand! She also had a bracelet made out of snow did not hurt her hands. The tip of her wand was a snowflake. Then Caroline came with some other fairies.
&amp;ldquo;This is Savannah the heat fairy, Willow the weather fairy, Dinah the draw fairy, Alice the animal fairy, Felicity the flower fairy, and Hannah the happy fairy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna, The New Ice Fairy Book # 1</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2861/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 17:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2861/</guid>
      <description>Anna went over to the stump where the tree was cut. Anna planted a tree which would grow in a long time. Anna was 6 now, when Anna was 16, Anna&amp;rsquo;s tree was fully grown! Sixteen year old Anna climbed up her tree. she saw a tiny girl with wings. &amp;ldquo;Hi! My name is Caroline! We saw you plant us a new home, this tree. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;I j-j-just wanted to replace th-th-the old tree that-t-t was c-c-c-cut down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Positive</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2761/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 17:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2761/</guid>
      <description>Positive the better
Only few are positive
So, try to make it better!
It makes everything
To be the better place
In the land of positive
Varsha
Expects this land to be positive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collection of Poems</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2721/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 14:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2721/</guid>
      <description>Colors, the wonderful,
Oh! Blue and gray, colors of sea,
Little girl enjoys those vast colors,
Oh! The earth is a colorful land,
All Red? No!
Everything is a different color,
So bright to make you smile.
Pink is life,
I love pink,
No pink, So much sadness,
Kept at the darkest color.
Blue the bright,
Living to be brilliant,
Up we go, to the brilliant blue sky,
EEK! Blue the beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Rainbows Formed</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3851/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 23:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3851/</guid>
      <description>One day, little Cassie walked across the pasture. The grass sparkled with the light of the Sun. The trees were entirely covered with blossoms. To Cassie, it felt like a dream. Cassie walked everyday, until she wanted color to the grass. Cassie would trade anything for colored grass. Suddenly an idea sprang up in her mind. She got her paint brushes and paints. Cassie painted the grasses like stripes of colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greedy Anne</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p3911/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 23:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p3911/</guid>
      <description>Anne Macolly was a magician. She had a wand. One day, she was thinking about what she wanted. She figured out. &amp;ldquo;I want something, just something magical. &amp;rdquo; Anne thought to herself, what magic words would make her magical thing. &amp;ldquo;AHBEEPREEGAW! &amp;rdquo; Yelled Anne. That was her magic words. Then suddenly a sparkling blue car appeared before her. Her gasp was heard by a man dressed in black.
&amp;ldquo;What a nice place to rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who inspired to make a Teddy Bear ?</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2581/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2581/</guid>
      <description>The Governor of Mississippi, Andrew.H Longino had invited Theodore Roosevelt for hunting. Theodore Roosevelt went on a hunting trip to Onward, Mississippi on November 14,1902. They didn’t seen a single bear to hunt. Holt Collier, who led Theodore’s assistants, captured a bear. Holt Collier asked Theodore to shoot the bear. But Roosevelt refused. News spread that the president did not obey the people who caught the bear. Clifford Berryman read the news and was inspired and made a cartoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fruit&#39;s Life</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2531/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 21:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2531/</guid>
      <description>I am a fruit.The farmer helped me grow.And I am an Apple. My friend Banana was also grown by by the same farmer. What a nice farmer! This is a story of a fruit&amp;rsquo;s life. One day (Apple was already grown) Banana had his father and mother go to work. Banana could not stay home alone. So our family took care of him. I was happy because Banana was my friend he was having a play date with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claude and the mystery of the stolen medal</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2511/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2511/</guid>
      <description>Claude strode back and forth, showing that he was bored. Claude was a detective. Suddenly Claude heard somebody shouting and calling his name. He followed the voice to Anetta, his neighbor. Claude saw that Anetta was looking tensed. &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s wrong Anetta? &amp;rdquo; Claude asked. Where was it? Where was it? &amp;ldquo;My camp medal was stolen! &amp;rdquo; Anetta shrieked. Claude thought for a moment. Why would someone take someone else&amp;rsquo;s medal? He is asking to himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chester and Owen</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2391/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 00:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2391/</guid>
      <description>Once there lived a very young koala bear, who did not like eucalyptus which was what koala bears eat. By the way, the young koala bears name was Chester. Chester never ate lunch lunch and dinner which was eucalyptus. That strike of food was making him starve. But finally he made friends with Owen Brown, a giraffe. He ate leaves from the maple tree and Chester loved the leaves. So,in the night Chester snuck to Owen&amp;rsquo;s house and ate ate leaves there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Bells</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2341/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2341/</guid>
      <description>Anna Maria squinted at the bell her wise grandmother gave her. It looked old. It was morning, and her grandmother&amp;rsquo;s banner glowed in the sunlight. &amp;ldquo;Old bell ha? &amp;rdquo; Anna Maria&amp;rsquo;s grand mother said, reading her expressions. Then grandmother started telling about The Student Council when she was young. &amp;ldquo;Our student Council elected some people to make bells to hang in the classrooms and I was chosen to make this bell &amp;ldquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUN</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 14:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2101/</guid>
      <description>Fun all around
Up in the air
Nothing but fun
I am having fun
Scattered around is fun
Georgious that fun is really fun
Really fun
Eat quickly you will have fun
After
Tea</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2081/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 14:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2081/</guid>
      <description>Amber was acting helplessly to the puzzle.She was annoyed because her sister Charlotte had gone out to play. Amber asked her mother to be excused out of the puzzle. She finally went outside and looked in her garage. Amber decided to ride her bike. She pulled her bike down the steep driveway, careful not to fall. After Amber was finished pulling her bike down, and rode her bike to Alissa&amp;rsquo;s drive way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parker</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 16:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2001/</guid>
      <description>Ania had a young dog named Parker. Parker sometimes got sick but it was not severe. When Nasha and Sam bullied Ania, a flush of disappointment and anger raged in her. As she went back home, she would go to her room upset, and her dog would come running to her. Parker would lick her all over Annia, it made her feel better. But it did not happen today. With in a minute Ania&amp;rsquo;s mother came in with a box with her eyes filled with tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope is Everything</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1971/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 16:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1971/</guid>
      <description>Hope is Everything
Seawater Beach was beautiful because the waves gently walked along its mushy border -the sand. Alissa, her mother and their dog Buttercup went along the beautiful beach. Alissa decided to make sand castles. Before they could make a sand castle, the waves suddenly rocked ferociously across it&amp;rsquo;s border.
Alissa&amp;rsquo;s dog Buttercup helplessly barked at the long, high, strides of desperate waves. Buttercup yanked the leash out of Alissa&amp;rsquo;s hands and disappeared into the waves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Yellow Yacht</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1901/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2013 23:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1901/</guid>
      <description>Dink, Josh and Ruth Rose were going to Costra(Yellow Yatcht) because their friend Sammi invited them to his birthday party. Sami showed his friends their room. Suddenly when Dink was choosing a room he saw a strange man peeking out of one room. They all went outside to explore the beech. Dink saw a yellow yacht with the green stripes just above the waterline. Then they heard an alarm sound from the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vampire&#39;s Vacation</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1851/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 20:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1851/</guid>
      <description>In the supermarket Josh finds a man who is very strange and looked like a vampire. Josh, Dink, Ruth Rose followed the strange man with in Josh&amp;rsquo;s idea. When they followed him outside, they saw him going in Ellie&amp;rsquo;s Diner but he never comes out. So Josh is persistent about finding about the mystery man. They went to the Ellie&amp;rsquo;s diner.When they talked to Ellie about the man, they saw a round bandage on her neck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gardeneeka&#39;s Smarts</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1761/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 22:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1761/</guid>
      <description>Once there lived a poor maiden named Gardeneeka. She set out trying to sell her most beautiful handkerchiefs, but no one bought them. Finally, one little girl pulled her mother towards the handmade handkerchiefs. Gardeneeka looked at the young girl&amp;rsquo;s mother with hopeful eyes, but the mother refused to buy the kerchiefs. So, the little girl&amp;rsquo;s mother angrily talked to her daughter about the kerchiefs while walking away. Gardeneeka hoped and hoped, but no one came to buy to the kerchiefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0 is a Hero!- a story with talking numbers</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1661/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 17:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1661/</guid>
      <description>1 heard a constant &amp;ldquo;thud, thud &amp;rdquo; coming from the number 0.
1 said to 2, &amp;ldquo; 0 does not belong here, he belongs to the negatives. Let&amp;rsquo;s throw him out of our group. Pass this message along to the other numbers, 2. &amp;ldquo;
So, the message went on until 10.
&amp;ldquo;You are right 1, let&amp;rsquo;s do it! YAHOO! &amp;rdquo; 10 said to 1.
&amp;ldquo;So throw him out of this group!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poems are Made</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1531/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 19:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1531/</guid>
      <description>Poems are Made
Poems are made because of the ideas
Poems are made to remember the forgotten things
Poems are made to burst out your happiness and make peace
Poems are made to stop the miserable things that come in your heart
Poems are made because of the wonderful nature which can be loved and shared
Poems are made to encourage and inspire children like me who are hungry for writing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Talented Clementine</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1501/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1501/</guid>
      <description>The Talented Clementine, by Sara Pennypacker and illustrated by Marla Frazee
Clementine thinks she has no talent when there is a talent show! Magaret tried to help her in tap dancing, but she could not. How did she get proud of herself,like 100%?
Read the book to find out.
For people who don&amp;rsquo;t think they have talents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends!</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1431/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 23:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1431/</guid>
      <description>When your small and new,
there are friends for you,
and there are friends for me,
like you see
so don&amp;rsquo;t fear
to be just a friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ant and The Snake</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1411/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 23:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1411/</guid>
      <description>One day in India, when there was no food,when there was a tiny cup with 7 grains of rice,lived one tiny ant. When he was strolling along the dry roads of India, a snake came up to him and said, &amp;ldquo;Eat the sssseven grainsss of ricessssss without asssissstacessss. &amp;rdquo; The snake&amp;rsquo;s name was Kaan. As soon as he strolled away, the ant gobbled up some grains of rice. Then he said to himself, &amp;ldquo;I will eat some rice tomorrow when Kaan won&amp;rsquo;t see me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hypnocycle</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1381/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 22:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1381/</guid>
      <description>You never got yourself straight on a hypnocycle,
Which feels like a bed,
That ol&amp;rsquo;e hypnocycle will doze your self to sleep,
Oh Joe, please don&amp;rsquo;t ride that again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother&#39;s Day!</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1311/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 14:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1311/</guid>
      <description>The lovely greetings that you&amp;rsquo;ll see
greetings great,
show all your faith in anyone you&amp;rsquo;d like,
you could do a hike,
and always be happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p1251/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p1251/</guid>
      <description>Love, Oh love, come back here and show yourself to my mom,
I&amp;rsquo;d be happy if you&amp;rsquo;d be calm,
Have fun,
With your smile as bright as the sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Poem</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p9071/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p9071/</guid>
      <description>I always want to improve,
When I always not sooth
When I waste a lot of food
in my grumpy mood
I always like to play
and that&amp;rsquo;s what I say
everyday.
My mom gives me math
My mom gives reading
and I never do seeding
I improve every time
I should give lime
and I help my mom
everytime when I can</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story of Grunting and Crying</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p81/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 11:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p81/</guid>
      <description>I grunt, I cry. There cannot be any solution. Could there just be one? There could if I stopped, there could if I stopped all unintelligible talks with comforting parents. Could I just show that I would stop? This should be comforting if i’d stop. Parents should not here small peels(cries) from me. Should I be positive or negative? POSITIVE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Parents love their sons or daughters if there is a lot of cooperation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sailor&#39;s Fish</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p421/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 01:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p421/</guid>
      <description>One day there was a sailor, who lived far away, in the land of Tanzeen. He mostly went on a boat called Seaville. The ocean he went was called The Everest Sea. His name was Collin Major. His family was very poor. He tried to sell Everest Sea’s fish, but all he caught was stinky fish. Collin knew he had to help him and his sea friends to get a lot of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poem</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p371/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 01:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p371/</guid>
      <description>I always want to improve when I always not sooth when I waste a lot of food in my very grumpy mood
I always like to play and that&amp;rsquo;s what I say everyday.
My mom gives me math, My mom gives me reading and I never do seeding
I improve every time I should give lime and I help my mom when ever I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albony, The Sunlight Child</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p341/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 01:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p341/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1 All about the Deconys Once upon a time, there was a little girl named Albony. Alobony had 2 sisters. The first sister was named Maria and the second sister was named Alissa. Albony, Alissa, and Maria’s last name was Decony. Albony was 7, Maria was 9, Alissa was 11.
The Decony’s were picking up troubles with their mom: like tattletaling, yelling, calling names, crying too much, and many other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mystery Of The Echoing Woods</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p321/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 01:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p321/</guid>
      <description>CHAPTER 1
One day there was a little boy named Jaylen. Jaylen lived in China near the Big Woods. One cold night, there was some echoing sound. It sounded like an animal was answering another animal. Jaylen knew that people were wondering about who were making those sounds that were coming from the Woods.
He also wanted to know who were making the sounds, like how the people of China wondered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The women with no face</title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/p2451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 00:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/p2451/</guid>
      <description>One day there was a boy named Mark. So one day Mark, he saw a women with no head and then when the women had a basket. Mark asked what is in that basket? Mark opened the basket then there was her head then Mark screamed after her head smiled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://varsham.github.io/posts/idontknow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://varsham.github.io/posts/idontknow/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>